

### **EDUCATION**

SOUTH-WEST UNIVERSITY "NEOFIT RILSKI" 15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 ( 4 years )

Bachelor's degree in Informatics

SOFTUNI "PRIVATE SOFTWARE UNIVERSITY" 05/12/2016 - 21/02/2018 ( 2 years ) Graduated C# and JavaScript engineer

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates/

# **ATANAS KAMBITOV**

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I offer 4 years of professional experience in software development.

At the moment I am working as a Full-time Software Engineer at Sainsbury's in the UK.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer with Cloud.

Programming is my passion, I also like getting involved in different areas such as Infrastructure, Cloud, Monitoring, Alerting, Reporting and more.

#### **PROJECTS**

.NET CORE AND REACTJS + TYPESCRIPT https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.backend https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.frontend

.NET CORE MVC https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

ANGULAR 2

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

#### LANGUAGES

ENGLISH, ITALIAN, SPANISH, BULGARIAN

#### CONTACT

PHONE: EMAIL: +44 744 87 19 858 atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

GITHUB & LINKEDIN: https://github.com/NASOKILA https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanas-kambitova69528162/

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer at Sainsbury's in Coventry, UK 03/12/2018 - Now (2 years)

Currently working on multiple projects mostly with C#, .Net Core, ReactJS, Typescript, React Hooks, Redux, SQL, TSQL, EF Core, Dapper, MongoDB, Azure, AWS, S3, SNS, Lambda, DevOps, AKS, Docker, Signal R, Key vaults, Storage accounts, AAD, Redis Cache, Container Registries, App Services, Azure Cosmos Databases, Service Bus, Event Hubs, REST API, SOAP, OOP and more.

Managing infrastructure using Terraform, Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment DevOps pipelines, container orchestration with Docker and Azure Kubernetes Cluster.

Experience in Microsoft365, Azure, Microservice architecture, Serverless architecture, Cloud-Native Apps, Full-stack development including unit, integration and automated UI testing with NUnit, XUnit and Selenium.

Usage of Power BI for reporting and Datadog for monitoring and alerting. Working in an agile way using scrum in a team of six people providing quality, latency, stability and performance carefully following solid principles and design patterns.

## Software Engineer at SoftUni in Sofia, Bulgaria

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Design and deliver backend RESTFUL API's using .Net Core and NodeJS + ExpressJS.

Build and release frontend applications with ReactJS and Angular2.

Experience with MVC, MVVM, REST, SOAP XML, JSON, YAML, Git, GitHub and more. Optimizing SQL queries and working on relational databases with SQL, MYSQL, Dapper and EF Core.

Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines on multiple projects using different technologies, languages and frameworks.